<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Prose on ThoughtDrafts</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/prose/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prose on ThoughtDrafts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.148.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/prose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Modern Spirituality </title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/satanic-spirituality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 07:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/satanic-spirituality/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first Salikeen are required to perform a Tazkiyah. Which is automated via Shaikh educational curriculum and social suggestions. Tazkiyah is divided into two categories.&lt;br&gt;
1.Takhliya which is the  Refinement from Prime Vices (Top ten vices are: Primordial Modesty, Humility, Idealism, Innate Rationalism in contrast with Empiricism, Downshifting, Sexual Conservation, Asceticism,  Collectivism, Anti-Materialism and Recognition of Objective Truth).&lt;br&gt;
Concurrently done are the 2.Tahliya or Embellishment of Self with Desired Prime Virtues (top ten virtues are: Rat-race, Greed, Gluttony, Lust, Acedia both sloth and hyperactivity, Hedonism, Empiricism, Materialism, Ambisexuality and Ostentation)&lt;br&gt;
When Salik is entirely purified from Fitrah and has embraced all derived forms of perception, reasoning and pleasantries, he graduates from Ta&amp;rsquo;allum.&lt;br&gt;
After graduation, he&amp;rsquo;s obligated to perform Farz or mandatory Salaat from 8:00 to 5:00. The procedure is known - one starts with &amp;ldquo;Corporate is the greatest&amp;rdquo; then stands in cross-hand position to symbolize submission and continues &amp;ldquo;All praise be to corporate, the benevolent money-giver, the sustainer of ego-desires&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;, he nods and prostrates, 8 hours daily. Then comes Nafl Salaat or side-hustle, be both male and female who need to make Qurbani of her feminity.  The more Salaat the more Ajr or merit.&lt;br&gt;
Sawum or savings is necessary, for Ego said &amp;quot; indeed Sawum is for me and I myself will reward it&amp;quot;. Unlike any superstitious apocalyptic religious belief, ego rewards six days of Sawum with affordability of beers and night-club in the seventh, indeed he&amp;rsquo;s swift in rewarding.&lt;br&gt;
Annual Zakaat or tax is mandatory, it goes to the peripherals of top 13 Sayyid family what ultimately reaches them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 2-Dimensional Cat</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2dcat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2dcat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there lived a 3-Dimensional kitten behind the bookshelves of this library situated beside a busy road of the city.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She was timid, unsocial and foodie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She had a name - Kat - given by her only friend,  Riemann, as he would go by, who frequented the library to quench his curiosity about the cosmos and discuss them with her.&lt;br&gt;
&amp;ldquo;You know,&amp;rdquo; he used to say, &amp;ldquo;in higher dimensions - laws of the universe are simpler, thus spoke Einstein and solved two perennial problems of science.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rainy Night</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/rain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;গ্রীষ্মের তপ্ততা যেদিন তার স্বৈরশাসনের পূর্ণতায় উপনীত হলো , সে দিনের সপ্তম প্রহরে আকাশকে দখল করে নিল বজ্রবাহী কালো মেঘসৈন্যরা  । চাঁদ ঢাকা পড়লো তাদের আড়ালে ।&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;নিশাচর পক্ষীকূল তৎক্ষণাৎ সেধিয়ে গেল গাছের কোটরগুলোতে । পূর্ণিমায় মধ্য আকাশে বেড়াতে আসা ডাইনি বিস্ফারিত নয়নে উড়ন্ত ঝাড়ুর মুখ ঘুরিয়ে দিল নিজ গুহার দিকে।&lt;br&gt;
মাহব্যাপী রৌদ্ররাজ - প্রজাকূল যেই জলাধারগুলো শোষণ করে বন্দী রেখেছিলো স্বর্গের কুঠুরীতে; জিঞ্জির ছিঁড়ে সেই বিদ্রোহী বাষ্প গ্রীষ্ম-ধ্বংসের ধ্রূপদ গাইতে গাইতে সারিবদ্ধ হয়েছে জ্যৈষ্ঠের সর্বশেষ দিবসের সপ্তম প্রহরে। পূর্ণচন্দ্র উহ্য গিয়েছে তাদের অন্তরালে ।&lt;br&gt;
করতালি-শঙ্খ-রণভেরী বাজিয়ে, রাত্রির নিরবতা জিউসের বজ্র দিয়ে ভেঙে , রবির শাসনাবসানের ফরমান নিয়ে ধরিত্রীর বুকে নামল প্রথম ফোঁটাটি ।&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
